What's more...
The amount of meat is so thin!
It's amazing how they cut it up into such small pieces.
Tomo and Pitcher, they ate all of it.
I can do it because I'm eating every day.
I'll do that.
Let's do our best.
Good evening, Bill!
Good evening, everyone.
As you can see, I'll be working hard on my shift.
Gb, gb, gb, gb.
I'm the newest member of Ebichu, but...
Well, I want the Devil's advocate to get his hands on it, so...
The first time we didn't have this kind of structure and we were still far away from this kind of thing.
I was nervous, but this week was totally different.
But this week was totally different.
everyone's been yodelling, "Do your best!" or "Inoki-San's 123!" or something like that
Well, let's bring the latest one to the live audience, shall we?
Well, you can call it yourself anytime you want.
Fire.
I'll have the proof.
I'm sure you'll be able to tell from the cheering...
I'll use "fire" as a call to action...
I'm going to use it for that event.
Let's go!
I don't know what it is, but it's true if you don't explain it.
I'm sure you'll be able to find out more about the details when you watch the broadcast.
Okay, let's start the recording.
Well...
Well, it's already...
It's not spring but early summer.
It's the first summer.
Mr. Gunn, are you new to this? Of course not!
Most adults in Japan call it "early summer.
Is there something like "early summer" in the background? Like, uh, symbols.
It's like a symbol... the state before the summer... before the full-blown summer...
the beginning of summer the beginning of summer the beginning of summer
It's hard to say, but it's early summer like that.
Today, I'd like to talk about it with you while looking at some pictures.
In early summer, the trees are green with leaves.
I have a tree in my neighborhood, do you know what kind of tree this is? This one...
A maple tree. May I ask you to leave?
I had a vague feeling it would get stuck one day.
It's been stuck every time I move, so I've always had a faint feeling...
Is he a clunker? No, no, no, it's a clunker.
I'm sure the fans of Ebitu have already noticed it.
It's written that it's a clunker.
It's a thick clodhopper. It looks delicious.
I'm a little jealous.
This is a plum tree. It's not red at all.
And as you all know, plums are used to make umeboshi (pickled plums) and such.
After the flowers are over, the fruits, which I'm sure you've all seen before, are like this.
You've probably seen them before... in green... and made into plum juice or plum wine.
Or adults make plum wine or something.
You know what the rainy season is, don't you?
I'm asking you.
That's great!
You surprised me.
It's like 4, 6, 3, 2 a month.
It was like two a month.
You know what I mean.
Okay, so it's two letters.
May I ask you to say them verbatim?
Rain?
Rain.
Rain 2, or rain, or rain, or rain, or rain, or rain, or rain, or rain, or rain.
The second letter down.
It's on top of rain.
Ume! Yes! Good! It means "plum rain" in Japanese.
So maybe this plum season is just around the corner, or maybe from now on.
May and June will probably be more and more prosperous.
Do you like pickled plums? I do.
I love them.
I don't know...
Sometimes I really want to eat them for free.
Yes, I do.
Oh! Like that.
I want some!
If you want, go pick some plums from someone's house.
I'm sure they're bitter.
Kate! I'd be like, "Oh, it's so bitter!
But I guess we are Japanese.
It's as if our DNA has been manipulated.
And then, what's next?
Ah! I'd like to give a quick update to the live audience.
Raiya Nakajima's new work, starting this week.
I've been calling him "yellow-green idiot" or "yellow-green refreshing idiot" or "yellow-green fresh idiot".
"Yellow Green Baka" or "Yellow Green Refreshing Baka" or "Mr. Knots".
I've been called "Mr. Knots"...
I don't know...
I'm not so sure about "Baka".
He says it's fine.
But from our point of view, calling someone an idiot...
Because they're idiots!
Hey! No!
I got a comment! Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much.
I was just wondering about that.
It's definitely refreshing, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
And I'm sure he's a clunker, too.
I think a clunker is a little cuter than an idiot.
That's why I decided to call him "Sawa-Pon" for short.
Sawapon for short.
Everyone, let's call him "Sawapon" from now on.
Sawapon, please.
My name is Sawapon.
I've got some pictures of Sawapon here.
Let's see this one here.
This one and this one are on the same topic.
This one first.
Okay, here we go.
This one.
Wow!
Here you go.
Seafood!
Yes.
Oh, yes.
What's the matter?
Just the other day my family went glamping together.
What's glamping?
I asked the same thing at the same time!
Now!
Let me explain it simply.
It's like a higher level of camping.
It's kind of like luxury camping.
Glamping is a place where everything is already prepared for you
You don't even need to bring anything.
Over there?
That's right.
You don't even need to bring your own food.
You don't even need a bed.
I see.
You'll be on your own.
That's right.
But the best part is that you can go with
The seafood.
That's dinner.
Dinner.
Yes, yes.
It's a little bit difficult for the live audience to sleep.
I know it's hard to sleep.
This is what it looks like.
Wow.
This is amazing.
That's what I'm talking about.
Shrimping.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
What is that thing over there?
That's Thailand.
Thailand!
Yes, sir.
Is it a medallion?
Amazing.
And a lobster.
That's amazing.
Did you do this on the beach or something?
Something like that.
Yes, at a glamping facility near the sea.
Glamping.
Like glamping, but in the style of glamping.
Yes.
That's the upper compatible.
You've learned.
I'm learning a lot, really.
It's alive.
I'm learning a lot.
It's all I know.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, and...
And the glamping facility.
And the glamping facility...
It has a sauna!
Isn't that amazing?
Isn't it amazing?
You can even do your own ronryu!
You can do it yourself.
Shuwah!
With a normal boatman, the water falls on its own.
so you're being swept away by the water on your own.
But in a place like this, you can do it by yourself.
Pouring water on the heated stone
You can do it by yourself.
And that's what it's all about.
I mean, it's still a camp, right?
That's right.
There's even a sauna!
Yes, it does.
What the heck!
It's almost like a hotel!
Oh, wow.
That was a lot of fun.
That's what "ronryu" means, isn't it?
It's often talked about in the sauna industry these days.
Water is poured on the hot stones and steam comes out.
And the steam makes you
and the steam makes you
That's what it's called
That's right.
Amazing!
I don't know...
Just hearing the name, it sounds like real Chinese.
I see.
I'm going to go to Nani Ryu.
Nani Ryu is definitely Chinese.
It sounds Chinese.
Nani Ryu.
Yes, sir.
Well, well, well.
I don't know...
It's like this, too.
It's so relaxing.
Do you tend to be pretty organized in your work?
I'm pretty organized.
Wow.
It feels good.
Does that mean...
Is it possible that...
Is there a water bath nearby?
Oh, yes.
Oh, yeah?
That's right.
That's amazing.
What do you mean?
It's all here.
Glamping is awesome!
So...
It's kind of divided into sections.
You can go outside and take a bath in the open air.
No problem!
That's right.
With your family.
I don't know...
I guess it's our age...
I mean, there's the time period, but...
We were a family...
I mean, we were little, but...
But as we grew up...
Especially when we were in our twenties...
I don't really go out with the family.
Like, "Wow!" kind of thing.
We didn't go anywhere at all.
Really?
In the Nakajima family...
Regularly.
The Nakajima family?
They get along well.
I've heard a lot about them.
Yes, they do.
What kind of family is it?
Yes, they are.
Imagine coming home...
We're all together.
I feel like we're still wandering around.
Not like that.
No, not like that.
Let's tune in.
First of all...
But yes...
My father was a bit of a clunker.
You have a lot of that in you.
That's right.
And your mother is a natural.
Yes, she is.
I can't do it.
I can't!
She's full of twists and turns.
That's right.
I can't do all that.
I can't do it alone.
You're down.
Just like that.
And your father...
Your mom's on your back.
Your mom's better.
That's right.
Your mom...
She's the king.
Mother...
My brother...
I'm a father
Dad...
You're not getting cold feet.
Oh...
Right.
Dad.
I knew it!
Pets are at the top of the list.
Pets are at the top.
I knew it.
It's like they're all worshipped and celebrated.
Was it a cat?
No, it's a dog.No, it's a dog.
It's a dog.
I mean, a dog?
Doesn't it get out of control?
But he's quite energetic.
He's a curious boy.
What do you mean, "curious"?
A miniature dachshund.
There it is.
He says he's out.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm still a miniature dachshund.
Really?
What?
You're a miniature dachshund.
Yes, we are.
They're cute, aren't they?
Like this.
Long and slender.
Yes, with short legs.
Ah!
He throws like this.
Ah! Yes, yes.
There are people who throw like this.
Sometimes there are people walking around like this.
Putting clothes on them like this.
Yes, that's right.
Like this.
That's right.
That's a miniature dachshund.
Wow!
That's the top of the line.
In terms of chilling chi.
Wow.
That's so cool!
I knew that animal was the one.
But it's definitely up there.
That's right.
Humans are only as good as Takada.
Takada can walk a little.
On two legs.
Animals are so much better.
Like speed?
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well...
And one more thing...
One more thing.
The other day...
I got this...
I got a strange e-mail from someone else.
Of course...
I didn't do a lot of things.
I'm not doing a lot of stuff, but...
I don't know what you're talking about.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Even if it's not converted
I wrote a lot of stuff after that.
I don't know what it's all about.
And now, all of a sudden...
In any case
I can feel the deliciousness of autumn eggplant
That's a beautiful word.
What?
What do you mean?
This is bad, isn't it?
This is bad.
Oh, it's like this, too.
They can come out of nowhere.
I want you to be careful.
Eeko...
Maybe it's some kind of scam.
Well, I'm sure it is.
Autumn eggplant?
Why all of a sudden?
But it still conveys the deliciousness of autumn eggplant.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's why...
I'll just...
Actually...
Kyushu tonkotsu ramen.
I love it.
I'm even attached to the word "ponkotsu".
I'm even a little attached to it.
and
and even more so when it comes to thick Ponkotsu.
Wow, seriously?
Bubbly? Like...
Bubbly? It's like...
And now, again...
Well, I've been there.
The Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group
Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group
Wow!
Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Kenkyukai
Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group
Turn
Cue
Cue.
It's a totally different feel.
So I'm on a daily trip around this neighborhood in search of Kyushu tonkotsu ramen.
This time, I went to Musashikosugi!
Musashi Kosugi is a very big town like this!
In front of the station, there are still towers and condominiums.
It's been about 10 years since I was here.
It wasn't so long ago.
But in the last few years, there have been a lot of new towers.
A lot of facilities have been built suddenly.
Musashi Kosugi was probably one of the top 10 places to live.
Musashi Kosugi is indeed very convenient.
Musashi Kosugi is also very convenient.
This is a store called "Vulture".
Vulture.
What?
It's a little scary, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
It's like eating ramen noodles and falling off.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That kind of thing.
That's not true at all.
I'm just visiting this place called Vulture.
It's just ramen...
Here you go.
Let's go.
Here we go.
Rashers!
May I?
I added a little more green onion.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no... when I first took a bite, I thought the soup was much lighter than I expected.
But the soup is very light... but when I think about it, it's the real Hakata Fukuoka ramen.
I've been there a few times, but it's not as thick as I imagined.
I think it's closer to gold.
Of course, it's like menkas...
So...
I'm sure you're right... the only thing he can't accept anymore is a wire.
I think he can only accept wires at the end of his body.
And then, of course, he ate it right away... and then, of course, there was the kaedama...
Kaedama is wonderful... it's good to have it in this kind of thing... right next to the ghee...
And the kaetama is a little bit more than a lot, isn't it?
Sesame seeds, takana and red ginger are added, and then it's poured into the bowl and eaten.
By the way, she sometimes puts her best effort into making the sesame paste, right?
I like this type of sesame most at ramen shops.
I call them "fishing type", but they're also called "fishing type".
It's like a fishing lure.
I'm going to turn it this way and say, "This is a version of this.
I'm sure you'll like this one, too.
I'm not sure if you can buy it, but I'm sure you can get it.
I wonder if the viewers are talking about the numbers.
I wonder if the viewers are talking about how the numbers are... like Master's numbers are fine.Master's numbers are like okay ahhhhh its so healthy that it's like ahhh ahhh
8, it's fine, it's not fine, it's fine.
I don't eat it every day, but once in a while, once in a while.
I'm not eating every day.
Master's very upset right now.
Don't worry... that's why I'm here.
If you have any information about this area, or Tokyo or anywhere else, please send it to us.
By the way, if you two have any information, well, I won't say it's too sudden, but yes...
I like Kyushu tonkotsu ramen so much that I founded the Kyushu Tonkotsu Ramen Study Group.
What would you like to study?
Anything is fine.
It could be an anime study group.
Bread and ice cream?
Bread and ice cream? That's good.
Panken for short. Panken.
Bread and ice cream... isn't this very deep?
It seems very deep, doesn't it?
Even if it's just bread, there's been a lot of good bread lately.
It's amazing.
I was surprised at how good bread is. When I ate that delicious bread, I was like, "What's this?
Well, you know, if you have a chance...
How many kinds of ice cream are there? There are so many, aren't there?
There's even a "Garigari-kun" and a "Baldy" for those who are bald.
By the way, in bedrock, there's ice cream here and bread there.
You can only eat one of them.
You can only eat one of them now.
This bread is your choice. Any kind of bread is fine.
And this ice cream over here, we have the one you like soooo much.
If you touch both the bread and the ice cream, the system will electrocute you.
Come on, it's like a golden axe, silver axe.
It's the ultimate quest.
It's either one or the other, right this minute.
If it's now, it's ice cream.
After I ate my lunch earlier, right?
That's right.
If it had been before I ate my lunch, I would've gone for the bread.
What about you, Sawamoto?
What should I do?
Maybe a sauna?
Maybe a sauna study group.
Sounds good.
I'm sure it depends on the place.
I'm sure it's totally different.
People often go to saunas.
I like the sauna association.
It's so neat.
If it's food...
I don't know.
Soba noodles or crab cream croquettes?
Crab cream croquette.
I love it.
It's not easy to eat it in a restaurant.
It's very hard to make it, isn't it?
You have to freeze it once.
Crab cream croquettes are very valuable.
That's good.
It looks good.
I'd like to follow you on location!
I love crab cream croquettes too.
But I have a cat tongue.
It takes me a long time to eat it right.
That's right.
Crab cream is very limited.
It's more like a crab cream croquette.
Right.
Crab cream croquette.
It's so good!
It seems to be very deep.
Well, well, well... that's why I'm here.
For those of you who are watching the live broadcast
I'd like to make an announcement.
As I mentioned last week
Saturday, May 6th
In the hall of the museum
LOL-chan's event will be held in the hall of the museum.
This is a free event, so please come and join us.
If you have time, please come!
Of course, LOL will be singing, dancing, and talking about all sorts of things.
And of course, LOL will be singing, dancing, and talking about all kinds of things.
I'm going to be there too.
I'm going to do something.
It seems like we're going to do something.
I see.
By all means, everyone!
May 6th.
About two weeks from now?
I hope you'll come.
May 6th is Rubber Day!
May 6th is Rubber Day.
Maybe.
Then let's all get together with our rubbers.
Let's all get together with our rubbers and yell "yay!
Like fire in the gundam.
It doesn't matter.
It's got nothing to do with anything.
It's got nothing to do with rubbers either.
That's what I'm talking about.
Okay, well, if you're watching the live broadcast...
I think it's time to go.
Tamamin's got an ice cream money for Ganbandany.
Devil's Charge.
Oh!
She sent it to me?
You sent me ice cream?
I'm so happy!
Wow.
Yes, indeed.
Thank you very much.
That's why.
Well, then...
I'll see you next week on the live broadcast.
Thank you very much for this week.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Do you want to do that one last thing?
Last one, please.
Okay, everybody, one last time.